you
I've been on the road for a million miles. I've
seen a thousand tears and a thousand fake
smiles. This engine's screaming, the diesel's
burning low. I've got nowhere left that I can go.
I'm tired of the fighting, sick of the lies Just
wanna see my own familiar skies Oh, won't you
take me home to Haven City Where the harbor
lights are burning pretty Oh, won't you please
just take me home, yeah
Yeah, take me home to Haven City Leave the broken
past for all to pity Oh, won't you please just
take me home?
See the harbor lights up through the mist I
promise that I can't resist Heard a con voice on
the telephone Said, boy, it's time that you came
on home I'm done with darkness Done with pain
Standing out in the pouring rain Oh, won't you
take me home to Haven City? where the harbor
lights are burning pretty oh won't you please
just take me home yeah
yeah take me home to haven city leave the broken
past for all to pity oh won't you please just take
me home
I
don't believe this.
Take me home. Won't you take me home? Take me
home. Won't you take me home? Take me home. Won't
you take me home? Take me home.
Take me home to the harbor lights burning
pretty. Take me home.
Won't you take me home?